Guide to the May Chen Papers WAG.301
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
May Chen Papers
1970-2017
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Chen, May Ying
WAG.301
28.06 Linear Feet in 37 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, 3 flat boxes, 3 oversized flat boxes, 1 cassette box, and 1 oversize folder.
30.85 Gigabytes on 8 CD-R, 4 CD-RW, 1 commercial DVD, 1 3.5 in floppy disk, and 8 DVD-R
5 videocassettes (vhs)
13 videocassettes (vhs-c)
4 videocassettes (minidv)
May Chen (1948- ) is a labor organizer who has done outreach and advocacy for immigrant workers since the 1980s. The materials in this collection relate to May Chen's work as a labor organizer and community activist in New York's Chinatown from 1989 to 2015. The collection includes materials related to sweatshop reform such as flyers, petitions and brochures. It also contains newspaper clippings (English and Chinese), conference materials, logistical planning documents for protests, meeting notes, contact lists, photographs, buttons, name tages, totebags, press releases, flyers, posters, and memos produced by the Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE) and the Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance (APALA). The other component of Chen's collection consists of advocacy work to aid Chinatown's economic recovery after 9/11.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
May Chen sent a gift of 7 boxes of her papers in 2009. The accession number associated with this gift is 2009.004. Chen sent an additional 3 boxes of papers relating to her work with the clothing industry in 2010. The accession number associated with this gift is 2010.091. In 2012, Tamiment received a donation of papers related to May Chen and Rocky Chin. One box of materials from this donation pertaining to May Chen were added to this collection. The accession number associated with these materials is 2012.008. May Chen donated an additional 11 boxes of her papers in 2018. The accession number associated with this gift is 2018.078.
Biographical Note
May Chen (1948- ) is a labor organizer who has done outreach and advocacy for immigrant workers since the 1980s. Born and raised in Boston, MA, she received her BA from Radcliffe College and her MA in Education at UCLA. While in California, Chen worked as a high school and adult education teacher, wrote for the Asian/Pacific/American (A/P/A) publications Gidra and Roots, founded a day care center that employed mainly immigrant women, and taught Asian and Asian American Studies at California State University, Long Beach.
Chen's involvement in the labor movement began in 1983 with her membership in Local 23-25 and her work on the International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU) Immigration Project beginning in 1984. The first union-initiated legal advocacy department for immigrant workers, the Immigration Project assisted thousands of union members in application for U.S. citizenship, sponsorship petitions on behalf of relatives, and legalization under the "amnesty" clause of the 1986 Immigration Reform and Control Act.
In 1989, Chen began a full-time position at Local 23-25's Education Department, coordinating labor education programs, English and Civics classes, voter registration and political action projects, and numerous other union and community activities for members. She became active in other labor-related groups, including the Coalition of Labor Union Women, on whose National Executive Board she served from 1984 to 1993, the Asian Labor Committee of the New York City Central Labor Council, and the AFL-CIO's Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance (APALA), of which she was a founding member and officer.
Until her retirement in June 2009, Chen served as International Vice President of UNITE HERE and Manager of Local 23-25. She also served as Secretary of the New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board.
Related Archival Materials
The papers of May Chen's husband, Rockwell "Rocky" Chin, are also located within the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives. See the Rocky Chin Papers (WAG.325).
Scope and Content Note
Most of the materials in this collection relate to May Chen's work as a labor organizer and community activist in New York City's Chinatown from 1989 to 2015. The collection contains newspaper clippings, logistic planning documents, meeting notes, contact lists, photographs, artifacts, press releases, flyers, conference materials, posters, and memos from UNITE meetings. The collection also reflects Chen's advocacy work to aid Chinatown's economic recovery after 9/11. These files include reports and conference materials relating to a variety of organizations, for example, Asian Americans for Equality's Rebuild Chinatown Initiative, the Asian American Federation's economic impact study of Chinatown after Sept 11th, and the Asian American Leadership Conference, "Healing and Rebuilding in New York," held on May 10, 2002. In addition, there are materials relating to Chen's work as a founding member and executive officer of the Asian-Pacific American Labor Alliance (APALA). These include a constitution and chapter by-laws, an application for tax exempt status, contact mailing lists, an executive board directory, and a directory of Asian-American organizations in New York and California.
Other materials in this collection include training guides, research materials, conference documents, pamphlets, and reports on Asian American labor rights and labor organizing. There is a large focus upon Asian American workers in the garment industry and workers in New York City's Chinatown including the work of organizations like the APALA, the Service Employees International Union (SEIU) - Local 1199, and the Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees and Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (UNITE/HERE) between the 1990s and early 2000s. There are also several travel journals and labor tour journals May Chen kept during trips to China and Japan between 1999 and 2011, as well as photo albums from Chen's travels and work in labor organizing.
The collection also includes memorabilia such as campaign and protest buttons, conference badges, and tote bags, as well as collected movies on VHS. Several original video recordings also feature footage of speeches, demonstrations, and conferences between 1988 and 2005, including footage of Jesse Jackson speaking in Chinatown in 1988 and footage from May Chen's travels to China and South East Asia.
Finally, the collection contains born-digital materials containing photographs and videos.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Arrangement
Materials in this collection are divided into four series.
Series I: Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees and Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (UNITE/HERE)
Series II: Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance (APALA)
Series III: Labor, Union, Conference, Political, and Research Materials and Reports
Series IV: Post-9/11 Chinatown and Lower Manhattan Development Corporation
Within each series, materials are organized alphabetically.
Born-Digital Access Policies and Procedures
Researchers may request access copies. To request that material be transferred, or if you are unsure if material has been transferred, please contact Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, special.collections@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Textile workers -- Labor unions -- 20th century; Asian Americans -- Economic conditions.; Asian Americans -- Social conditions.; Women labor leaders.; Minority labor union members.; Photographs.; Posters.; Research notes.; Political campaigns.; Labor movement -- New York (N.Y.); New York (N.Y.).; Chinatown (New York, N.Y.); September 11 Terrorist Attacks, 2001.; Newspaper columns.; Colloquia and conference papers; Brochures.; Newsletters.; Circulars (fliers); Video recordings.; Chen, May Ying; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance; Dinkins, David N.; Chin, Rocky, 1947-; Lower Manhattan Development Corporation; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees. Local 23-25 (New York, N.Y.)
- Series I: Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees and Hotel Employees and Restaurant Employees International Union (UNITE/HERE), 1983-2013; 4.79 Linear Feet in 10 manuscript boxes, 2 flat boxes, 1 oversized flat box, and 1 cassette box
  Scope and Contents
  This series focuses upon May Chen's advocacy work to aid unionized workers, particularly in Chinatown's garment industry, via her involvement as a representative of the Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE) Local 23-25 and the Hotel Employees and Resturant Employees (HERE) International Union. Materials in this series include, but are not limited to, anti-sweatshop documents in both English and Chinese, rally posters, educational circulars, photographs, petitions, UNITE memos, copies of UNITE newsletters, Chinese news publications, research statistics, and zoning information focused upon the garment district. This series also includes some audiovisual and born-digital items.
  - 8/28/98 Rally, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1-2, Box Shared Tamiment 150, Folder 6)
  - 8/28/98 Rally Press Clippings, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
  - 2006 China Trip UNITE HERE & SEIU/2008 Chin-Wang Reunion, 2006, 2008 (Box 39, Minidv 301.0019)
  - Apparel, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Apparel Industry Task Force, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Apparel Industry Task Force (UNITE/HERE), 2005 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Asian Americans for Equality (UNITE!), 1998, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Asian American Federation of New York - Economic Characteristics of Asian Americans in New York Metropolitan Area, 2005-2007 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Asian American Federation of NY (AAFNY) Research, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Bio/Personal (May Chen), 1998-2010 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bloomberg '05, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Blouse Guideline (UNITE), undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Building Bridges Conference, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Buttons, undated (Box 41)
  - Calendar of Public Hearings on Contract Awards, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Carl Proper/1710 Memos, 1997-2001 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Change to Win Coalition, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
  - Change to Win Meeting, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Change to Win National Organizing Leadership Conference in Las Vegas, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - China, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - China Safeguards, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Chinatown Garment Industry Study, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Chinese News, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Chinese Press Clips (UNITE), 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - City Support, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Consortium for Worker Education, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - Asian American Federation of New York, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - International Textile, Garment, & Leather Worker's Federation, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Daily Newspaper, 1999-2001 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Education, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Eileen Fisher, 1999-2001 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Forms - Job Training Questionaire for UNITE Members, undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Garment Center Rezoning & Revitalization, 1992, 2003, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Garment Center Zoning, 2004-2007 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Garment District Post 9/11, Rebuilding New York, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Garment Industry Development Corporation, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Garment Worker Oral History Interviews, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Garment Workers & Sweatshops, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - GIDC, MINY, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - "GIDC - Ron Karpman Reports", 2000, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Guess Campaign, 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Hot Line 96-97, 1997, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride Chinatown Press Conference, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
  - Industry, 1997-1999, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Japan Trip, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Job Training Classes, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - July 29 Rally/Lobby, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - L23-25 Members Leader File 3/06, 2006; cuid36473 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_WAG_301_ER_4)
  - Labor Tours: Tote Bag and Gift Plate from Guangzhou Labor Union, undated (Box 40)
  - Local 23-25 Cash Voucher - Shop Activist Meeting Member Lists, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Local 23 25 Lunar New Year Dinner 03-12-2004, cuid36476 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_WAG_301_ER_7)
  - Local 23-25 Scholarship, 2000-2003 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Local 23-25 UNITE!, 1991, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - MAA, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - May Y. Chen, 1998, 2002, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - May Ying Chen Biographical Information, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - May Chen Nametags, undated (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
  - New York Fashion Space, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - New York Fashion Space Executive Summary, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - The New York Immigration Coalition, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board UNITE! Pamphlet, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - NYIRN, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - NY State Hearing About Unemployment (7/8/2005) (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - NYC - AICP, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - NYC's Garment Industry - A New Look?, 2003-2004 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Organize! Mobilize! Unite! Poster, undated (Box Shared Tamiment 150, Folder 8)
  - Photograph - UNITE!, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Photographs, 1986-1990, 1992, 1995-1996, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Photographs - UNITE and Hillary Clinton, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Photo Album - Labor Tour of Japan, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Pre-Retirement Seminar (UNITE), 1997 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Press Release - Labor Dispute Against Firm of Tracy Evans (UNITE), undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - SAA, 1998-1999, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Sep. 18 Hearing - Asian Community (White House & UNITE), 2000 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Shopping Guide - Where to Buy Made in New York Pamphlet (UNITE!), 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - State of New York Department of Labor, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Statements and Testimonies, 1999-2001 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Sweatshops, 1998-2002 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - "Textile/Fiber Coalition Wins Victory on China Safeguards", 2003 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Trade Union Ephemera, 1990, 1992, 2013 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Unemployment Insurance Issues, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - UNITE!, 2004-2007 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - UNITE! - 100 Years (1900-2000), 2003 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - UNITE: Basic Steward Training Manual, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - UNITE Convention - Local 23-25 Delegation Group Photo, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - UNITE Directories, 2001, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - UNITE Event with Hillary Clinton/Fix '96 Campaign, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - UNITE Here! Activist Pin, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - UNITE Here! National Retirement Fund Brochure, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - UNITE Here!: Retirement Party, 2008; cuid36480 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_WAG_301_ER_13)
  - UNITE Here Solidarity Relief for 2008 China Earthquake Victims (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - UNITE Immigration Project, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - UNITE - Instructional Materials for How to Organize Meetings, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - UNITE! - Knitgoods Workers' Union Local 155 Newsletter, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - UNITE! - Local 23-25 Newsletter, 1997-2003 (Box 9, Folder 1-3)
  - UNITE! - New York Metropolitan Area Joint Board Newsletter, 2004-2006 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - UNITE! Newsclippings, 2008 (Box Shared Tamiment 150, Folder 4)
  - UNITE Pre-Retirement Seminar, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - UNITE! - Proudly Made in New York Bookmarks, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - UNITE - Reading Matter, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - UNITE! Retiree Service Department, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - University of Massachusetts - Amherst Labor Studies Materials, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 10, Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Various UNITE! Papers, 2000-2003 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Women's Apparel Inc. Task Force, 1999-2002 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Women's Apparel Inc. Task Force Meeting Materials (UNITE), 1999 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Workers' Center (UNITE!), undated; cuid36467 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Zoning & GC, 2003, 2007, 2009; cuid36468 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Series II: Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance (APALA), 1992-2015; 2 Linear Feet in 5 manuscript boxes and 1 oversized flat box
  This series focuses upon May Chen's invovlement with the Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance (APALA); Chen was a founding member and executive officer. Materials include administrative documents, artifacts, mailing lists, APALA Board Meeting minutes, campaign information, press releases, powerpoint presentations, conference materials, demographic and political statistics, as well as voter education manuals.
  - APALA, 2004-2014 (Box 10, Folder 7-8, Box 11, Folder 1-2)
  - APALA 8th Biennial Convention, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - APALA 9th Biennial Convention, 2007 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - APALA 10th Biennial Convention, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - APALA 10th Bienniel Convention Tote, undated (Box 40)
  - APALA 11th Biennial Convention, 2011 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - APALA 2007 Convention (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - APALA 2010 Report & 2011 Goals (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - APALA, AFL-CIO Executive Board Meeting, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 9, Box 12, Folder 1)
  - APALA, AFL-CIO Political Education Conference, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - APALA - Chapter By-Laws, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - APALA Chapter Membership Report, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - "APALA Condemns Terrorist Attacks and Calls for Unity and Tolerance", 2001 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - APALA Congressional Voter Guide, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - APALA Constitution, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - APALA Constitutional Convention, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - APALA Executive Board Meeting, 2004-2005, 2007, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 9-11, Box 13, Folder 1-2)
  - APALA Founding Convention WDC-ILG Delegation, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - APALA Membership, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - APALA Membership Brochure, 2010, 2015 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - APALA Memos, 2000 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - APALA New York Chapter, 1997-1999 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - APALA Old Files, 1996, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - APALA Papers, 2005-2007 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - APALA - Tax Status - Ein, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Asian Pacific American Heritage Month - A Concise History (APALA), undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance Women's Organizing Institute, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Breaking Ground, Breaking Silence: Reports from the First National Asian Pacific American Workers' Rights Hearing, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Celebrating APALA's First Decade: Continuing the Fight for Worker Justice, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Diversity and Change: Asian American and Pacific Islander Workers, 2011 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Japanese Union Reps and Individuals Attending APALA Convention, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Making America Work: Asian Americans, Native Hawaiians, and Pacific Islanders in the Workforce and Business, 2014 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - New York Asian-American/Pacific Islander Worker Protection Summit, 2010-2011 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Strengthening Our Voices for Worker Rights, Immigrant Rights, and Civil Rights (APALA National Convention), 2003 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - The Unity Slate (APALA), undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Series III: Labor, Union, Cultural, Research, Conference, and Political Materials and Reports, 1970-2017; 20.06 Linear Feet in 21 manuscript boxes, 1 flat box, 1 oversized folder, 4 oversized flat boxes, 1 half manuscript box, and 1 cassette box
  Series III focuses upon the improvement of the garment district in New York City, garment industry reform, conferences, protests, women's role in labor movements, Asian and Asian American communities, New York City politics, and the Triangle Shirtwaist Factory Fire. Materials include photographs, tote bags, newspaper clippings, brochures, flyers, posters, educational course materials, and petitions. This series also contains audiovisual and born-digital materials.
  - 3 Kings Celebration, 1996 (Box 39, Vhs-c 301.0007)
  - 9th Annual General Meeting of NUGW Tokyo South Annual Policy for 2002 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - The 10th Chinatown Labor Fair Poster, 1993 (Box Shared Tamiment 079, Folder 33)
  - 16th National Conference on Women and the Law, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - 95 Jing Fong, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - 96 School Board Complaint, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - 96 Welfare Reform, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - 1199 CAT, 2015 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - 1199 Chinese Activist Training: Language Training Exercises, 2015 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - 1199 Chinese Activist Training: Readings, 2004-2005 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - 1199 Chinese Activist Training: Unions in New York City, 2010-2011 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - 1199 SEIU Home Care Division - Chinese Activist Teacher Training, 2015 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - 1199 SEIU News Magazine, 2002 (Box Shared Tamiment 080, Folder 13)
  - 1970's 1980's Lit on Asian Americans and Asian Struggles, 1971-1972, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - 1982 Garment Strike, 2012 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - 1989 CPA Voter Skit (Box 39, Vhs-c 301.0006)
  - 2002 Fashion Bid Report (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - AAHEC Leadership Conference, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Aaron's Jokes, 1993, 1996-1998 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - AFL-CIO Civil Rights Conference, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - AFL-CIO Pre-Convention Conference, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Ameco Beijing Annual Report, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - America @ Work: The Face of the New Economy, 2005 (Box Shared Tamiment 080, Folder 15)
  - The American Citizens for Justice Yearbook Vincent Chin Murder, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - American Friends Service Committee, 1993, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - American Sons, undated (Box 38, Vhs 301.0002)
  - AMPO Japan-Asia Quarterly Review, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - APSU (Asian Pacific Student Union), 1981-1982, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Asia Conf., 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Asia Students in Action, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Asian American Access to Democracy I nthe 2008 Elections (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Asian Americans and the "American Dream" 1984 East Coast Asian Student Union (ECASU) Conference, 1984-1986 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Asian American/Asian Research Institute City Univeristy of New York, 2016 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Asian American Bar Association, 2002-2006 (Box 16, Folder 9-10)
  - Asian American Bar Association of New York (AABANY), 1991-1992, 1998, 2003, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 11-12)
  - Asian Americans for David Dinkins (AADD)/AABNY, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Asian American Elders in New York City, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Asian American Federation of New York: Report on Asian American Mental Health, 2003 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Asian American Leadership Conference: Healing & Rebuilding New York, 2002; cuid36486 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_WAG_301_ER_20)
  - Asian American Organizations: New York, 1991-2002, 2010, 2013 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Asian American Organizing: Reports and Action Plans, 1986-2012 (Box 17, Folder 4-7, Box 18, Folder 1)